{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867951323","data":{"timestamp":" 946867951323"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_055135"," gameId":" cfb0cd84-bde6-4149-a27b-b4020c76bfba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867954974","data":{"timestamp":" 946867954974"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_055135"," gameId":" cfb0cd84-bde6-4149-a27b-b4020c76bfba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867964278","data":{"timestamp":" 946867964278"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_055135"," gameId":" cfb0cd84-bde6-4149-a27b-b4020c76bfba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867966657","data":{"timestamp":" 946867966657"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_055135"," gameId":" cfb0cd84-bde6-4149-a27b-b4020c76bfba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867976698","data":{"timestamp":" 946867976697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_055135"," gameId":" cfb0cd84-bde6-4149-a27b-b4020c76bfba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867978397","data":{"timestamp":" 946867978396"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_055135"," gameId":" cfb0cd84-bde6-4149-a27b-b4020c76bfba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867987098","data":{"timestamp":" 946867987098"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_055135"," gameId":" cfb0cd84-bde6-4149-a27b-b4020c76bfba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867989157","data":{"timestamp":" 946867989157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_055135"," gameId":" cfb0cd84-bde6-4149-a27b-b4020c76bfba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867997447","data":{"timestamp":" 946867997447"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_055135"," gameId":" cfb0cd84-bde6-4149-a27b-b4020c76bfba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867999866","data":{"timestamp":" 946867999866"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_055135"," gameId":" cfb0cd84-bde6-4149-a27b-b4020c76bfba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868018824","data":{"timestamp":" 946868018824"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_055135"," gameId":" cfb0cd84-bde6-4149-a27b-b4020c76bfba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868024672","data":{"timestamp":" 946868024672"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_055135"," gameId":" cfb0cd84-bde6-4149-a27b-b4020c76bfba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868032547","data":{"timestamp":" 946868032546"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_055135"," gameId":" cfb0cd84-bde6-4149-a27b-b4020c76bfba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868040588","data":{"timestamp":" 946868040588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_055135"," gameId":" cfb0cd84-bde6-4149-a27b-b4020c76bfba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868051142","data":{"timestamp":" 946868051142"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_055135"," gameId":" cfb0cd84-bde6-4149-a27b-b4020c76bfba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868053789","data":{"timestamp":" 946868053789"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_055135"," gameId":" cfb0cd84-bde6-4149-a27b-b4020c76bfba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868062711","data":{"timestamp":" 946868062710"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_055135"," gameId":" cfb0cd84-bde6-4149-a27b-b4020c76bfba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868069871","data":{"timestamp":" 946868069870"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_055135"," gameId":" cfb0cd84-bde6-4149-a27b-b4020c76bfba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868071885","data":{"timestamp":" 946868071885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_055135"," gameId":" cfb0cd84-bde6-4149-a27b-b4020c76bfba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868085585","data":{"timestamp":" 946868085585"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_055135"," gameId":" cfb0cd84-bde6-4149-a27b-b4020c76bfba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868092538","data":{"timestamp":" 946868092538"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_055135"," gameId":" cfb0cd84-bde6-4149-a27b-b4020c76bfba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868100055","data":{"timestamp":" 946868100055"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_055135"," gameId":" cfb0cd84-bde6-4149-a27b-b4020c76bfba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868102760","data":{"timestamp":" 946868102760"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_055135"," gameId":" cfb0cd84-bde6-4149-a27b-b4020c76bfba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868112084","data":{"timestamp":" 946868112083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_055135"," gameId":" cfb0cd84-bde6-4149-a27b-b4020c76bfba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868118460","data":{"timestamp":" 946868118460"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_055135"," gameId":" cfb0cd84-bde6-4149-a27b-b4020c76bfba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868126062","data":{"timestamp":" 946868126062"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_055135"," gameId":" cfb0cd84-bde6-4149-a27b-b4020c76bfba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868128736","data":{"timestamp":" 946868128736"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_055135"," gameId":" cfb0cd84-bde6-4149-a27b-b4020c76bfba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868143789","data":{"timestamp":" 946868143787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_055135"," gameId":" cfb0cd84-bde6-4149-a27b-b4020c76bfba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868161910","data":{"timestamp":" 946868161910"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_055135"," gameId":" 39a9ce92-5968-48d9-b7ad-439fb1902e00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}